DARREN BEHAN







6/18 Kensington Road, South Yarra, VIC, 3141

darrenbehan@hotmail.com

0435 399 232

PROFILE

My focus is to deliver a professional, efficient & consistent customer experience with continuous development to the systems in use to support this approach.

Throughout my career, I have maintained a high level of consistency when servicing internal and external stakeholders to ensure each received the attention required. Honesty, hard-work and passion are but a few values that I continuously live by and have pushed me to reach new heights throughout various roles.

EXPERIENCE

Accounts Payable Officer

REA Group August 2018 - Present

The core function of my role is to ensure our vendors receive payment for the goods & services provided within their credit terms whilst continuously seeking opportunities to improve the processes & systems surrounding this.

By questioning the status quo, we were able to re-develop our monthly reporting with the use of existing systems reporting capabilities which produces consistent and detailed automated reports.

Re-designing the Accounts Payable NetSuite dashboard has contributed to consistent processing and ensuring we meet the controls set by the group.

Further critical skills gained to date from the Finance System (NetSuite) Support team to benefit our team was the ability to create searches & perform bulk uploads. This allows our team to reduce manual, time-consuming processes reducing the turnaround times in various areas such as vendor creation for the Advantage Plus program.

EDUCATION

Certificate in Payroll & Bookkeeping 2009

Clane College

Bachelor of Business (Honors) Degree in Accounting 2006-2011

Institute of Technology Carlow

CORE

- Maintain strong stakeholder relationships
- Zendesk, Salesforce, NetSuite, SAGE CRM
- MS Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Outlook
- Coding skills: Ruby, Rails, JavaScript, React
- Continuously striving to improve processes across the broader team

DARREN BEHAN



Darren Behan



@darren_behan



Linkedin Profile

EXPERIENCE

Credit Controller

REA Group August 2017 - 2018

The key functions of my role were as follows:

- To manage a ledger of 2,800+ accounts ensuring the daily sales outstanding is kept within the KPI's set for the Credit team.
- Liaised with key stakeholders to implement Zendesk replacing a legacy system.
- Utilised the Finance System (NetSuite) to maintain customers' accounts such as processing payments & generating invoices.
- Advocate for driving change to outdated & manual processes within the Credit team.

Customer Service Consultant

REA Group 2016 - 2017

The key functions of my role were as follows:

- Service all stakeholders through various channels of communications such as phone, email and live chat.
- Be proactive consistently to avoid queue wait times increasing.
- Train new employees by being a point of contact
- Assisted in implementing Zendesk & SPOT.
- Participate in all process improvement by providing regular feedback.

ACHIEVEMENTS

- Implementation of Zendesk for the Credit and Australian Finance team
- Rolling out a dominant Marketing structure for the Keilor Hotel
- Obtaining a Degree in Accountancy
- Achieving Australian Citizenship
- Volunteer work inside and outside of REA Group

REFEREES

Ω

Esther Monks

Finance Manager

esther.monks@reagroup.com Harr Yate

Credit Manager

harriet.yates@rea-group.com

 \mathcal{R}

Rvan Anderson

Customer Care Team Leader

ryan.anderson@realestate.com.au